<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on My New Hugo Site</title>
    <link>https://example.org/posts/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on My New Hugo Site</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 16 Jan 2024 17:50:54 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://example.org/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Data Pipeline</title>
      <link>https://example.org/posts/data-pipeline/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Jan 2024 17:50:54 -0700</pubDate>
      <guid>https://example.org/posts/data-pipeline/</guid>
      <description>Project Overview This project will simulate a end to end data pipeline for Data First Jobs. It will consist of the following tools: * Kafka * Airflow * DBT * Metabase&#xA;I built Data First Jobs because not only was I tired of filtering through multiple job boards, but many of those job board did not consistenlty categorize data jobs. In other words, sometimes there were under &amp;ldquo;other&amp;rdquo;, somethings they were under engineeers, but usually they were a mix and few and far between.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ansible</title>
      <link>https://example.org/posts/ansible/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Jan 2024 12:10:46 -0700</pubDate>
      <guid>https://example.org/posts/ansible/</guid>
      <description>Ansible When I first moved away from PaaS platforms like Heroku and Render, it quickly became daunting running a VPS manually. Eventually I stumbled upon Ansible.&#xA;Ansible helps automate your server instances, it can manage your servers or hosts from a single workstation. The best part about it is that you don&amp;rsquo;t need to host it on a server, instead you can run it straight from your laptop.&#xA;Getting started with Ansible Ansible allows you to ssh into your servers and carry out commands defined in what&amp;rsquo;s called a &amp;ldquo;playbook&amp;rdquo;.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DF Jobs Architecture</title>
      <link>https://example.org/posts/df-jobs-architecture/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Jan 2024 12:10:46 -0700</pubDate>
      <guid>https://example.org/posts/df-jobs-architecture/</guid>
      <description>DF Jobs Data First Jobs is a job board for data professionals across industries, tech stacks, and more.&#xA;It pulls data from third-party job board apis, parses their data and maps it to my apps models using a json schema.&#xA;I&amp;rsquo;ve built an internal as well as an external API. The internal API serves the jobs to my front end, using just vanilla js, whereas the external one will just be used to expose jobs that are posted directly on DF Jobs (none currently).</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
